A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1963-1964, 3; 37 Cubic Feet
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kom), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1340)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Kr), 1964 (Box 50, Folder 1341)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1342)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lam), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1343)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lar), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1344)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lav), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1345)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Le), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1346)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Leh), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1347)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lem), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1348)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lev), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1349)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Li), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1350)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lo), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1351)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lor), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1352)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lu), 1964 (Box 51, Folder 1353)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Lur), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1354)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1355)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mak), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1356)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1357)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence, 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1358)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mat), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1359)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Maw), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1360)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mc), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1361)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McD), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1362)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McK), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1363)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McM), 1964 (Box 52, Folder 1364)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (McS), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1365)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Me), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1366)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mek), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1367)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Men), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1368)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mes), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1369)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mi), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1370)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mik), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 1371)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mik), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 1372)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Min), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1373)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mir), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1374)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mo), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1375)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mom), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1376)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mor), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 1377)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mor), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 53, Folder 1378)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mot), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1379)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mu), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1380)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Muk), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1381)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Mur), 1964 (Box 53, Folder 1382)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1383)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ne), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1384)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ni), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1385)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (No), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1386)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Nu), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1387)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1388)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ok), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1389)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Om), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1390)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Or), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1391)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ov), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1392)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (P), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1393)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pal), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1394)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Par), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1395)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pav), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1396)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pe), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1397)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pel), 1964 (Box 54, Folder 1398)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Per), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1399)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pev), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1400)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ph), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1401)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pi), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1402)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pir), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1403)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Po), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1404)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Por), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1405)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pov), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1406)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pr), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1407)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pu), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1408)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Pur), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1409)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Q), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1410)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Quo), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1411)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Jackie Robinson, 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1412)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1413)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ral), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1414)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rar), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1415)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Re), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1416)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rei), 1964 (Box 55, Folder 1417)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rel), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1418)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rer), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1419)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rh), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1420)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ri), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1421)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ril), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1422)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ro), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1423)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Roc), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1424)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Roc), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1424A)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rol), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1425)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ror), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1426)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rov), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1427)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ru), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1428)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rul), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1429)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Rur), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1430)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ruv), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1431)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1432)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sak), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1433)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sam), 1964 (Box 56, Folder 1434)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sar), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1435)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sav), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1436)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sc), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1437)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sch), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1438)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Schi), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1439)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Schm), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1440)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sho), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1441)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Schu), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1442)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Se), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1443)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sek), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1444)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sen), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1445)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sh), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1446)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (She), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1447)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Si), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1448)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sik), 1964 (Box 57, Folder 1449)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sin), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1450)
    General note
    Water Damage - Handle With Care
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sir), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1451)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sl), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1452)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sm), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 1453)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sm), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 58, Folder 1454)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sn), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1455)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (So), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1456)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sp), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1457)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (St), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1458)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ste), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1459)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sti), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1460)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Stow), 1964 (Box 58, Folder 1461)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Stu), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1462)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Su), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1463)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Sum), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1464)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Suw), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1465)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1466)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tal), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1467)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tar), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1468)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Te), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1469)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Th), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1470)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ti), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1471)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tir), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1472)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (To), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1473)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tor), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1474)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tr), 1964 (Box 59, Folder 1475)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Tu), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1476)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (U), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1477)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1478)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Ve), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1479)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Vi), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1480)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Vo), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1481)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (W), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1482)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wal), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 1483)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wal), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 1484)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (War), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 1485)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (War), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 60, Folder 1486)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Was), 1964 (Box 60, Folder 1487)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 60, Folder 1488)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 1489)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (We), 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 1490)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wer), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1491)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wh), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 1492)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wh), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 61, Folder 1493)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wi), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1494)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wil), 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 1495)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wil), 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 1496)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wil), 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 61, Folder 1497)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wim), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1498)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wo), 1964 (Box 61, Folder 1499)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Wor), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 1500)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (X), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 1501)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 1502)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Z), 1964 (Box 62, Folder 1503)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 1504)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 1505)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 1506)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 1507)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 62, Folder 1508)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 62, Folder 1509)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 1510)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 1511)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 1512)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 1513)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E), 1964 (Box 63, Folder 1514)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 1515)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 63, Folder 1516)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 1517)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 63, Folder 1518)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (G), 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 1519)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1964 (Box 64, Folder 1520)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I), 1964 (Box 64, Folder 1521)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 1522)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 1523)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 1524)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 64, Folder 1525)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1964; Folder 1 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 1526)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1964; Folder 2 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 1527)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1964; Folder 3 of 3 (Box 64, Folder 1528)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1964; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 64, Folder 1529)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1964; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 65, Folder 1530)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1964; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 65, Folder 1531)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1964; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 65, Folder 1532)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N), 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1533)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (O), 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1534)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 1535)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (P), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 1536)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Q), 1964 (Box 65, Folder 1537)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 65, Folder 1538)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 1539)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1964; Folder 1 of 4 (Box 66, Folder 1540)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1964; Folder 2 of 4 (Box 66, Folder 1541)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1964; Folder 3 of 4 (Box 66, Folder 1542)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1964; Folder 4 of 4 (Box 66, Folder 1543)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 1544)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 1545)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (U-V), 1964 (Box 66, Folder 1546)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W-Z), 1964; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 1547)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W-Z), 1964; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 66, Folder 1548)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Miscellaneous Postcards, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 1549)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 1 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1550)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 2 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1551)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 3 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1552)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 4 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1553)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 5 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1554)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 6 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1555)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 7 of 11 (Box 67, Folder 1556)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 8 of 11 (Box 68, Folder 1557)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 9 of 11 (Box 68, Folder 1558)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 10 of 11 (Box 68, Folder 1559)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1964; Folder 11 of 11 (Box 68, Folder 1560)
- 1965, 1967, 4; 8 Cubic Feet
  This subseries has correspondence from 1965 and 1967. There are no materials from 1966.
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1561)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1562)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Broome County Republican Committee 1965 Yearbook (Box 68, Folder 1563)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (C), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1564)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - Columbus Day Unveiling - Organization - October 12, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1565)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (D), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1566)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (E), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1567)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (F), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1568)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (G), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1569)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (H-I), 1965 (Box 68, Folder 1570)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (J), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1571)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (K), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1572)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (L), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1573)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (M), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1574)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (N), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1575)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (O-Q), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1576)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (R), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1577)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (S), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1578)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (T-U), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1579)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - United Republican Finance Committee, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1580)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (V-W), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1581)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Y-Z), 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1582)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - October 4th Dinner - New York Republican State Committee, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1583)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer - Anonymous, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 1584)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (A), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1585)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (B), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1586)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C-D), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1587)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E-G), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1588)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H-I), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1589)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J-K), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1590)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1591)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1592)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N-Q), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1593)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R-S), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1594)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (T-Z), 1965 (Box 70, Folder 1595)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (A), 1967 (Box 70, Folder 1596)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Al), 1967 (Box 70, Folder 1597)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (An), 1967 (Box 70, Folder 1598)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (B), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1599)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Be), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1600)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bi), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1601)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bo), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1602)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence (Bu), 1967 (Box 71, Folder 1603)